[
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "09_getoffbeach",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 1,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0901_0100_d_00_container_getoffbeach",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0901_Watcher",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 9,
        "AchievementId": "S_getoffbeach",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "S_getoffbeach_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@title_getoffbeach",
        "Description": "@desc_getoffbeach",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@prompt_DEFAULT",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@proposal_getoffbeach",
        "InProgressResponse": "@incomplete_getoffbeach",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0900_0101_getoffbeach_complete_availaible_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0901_0101_culldrowned",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0901_0101_d_00_container_culldrowned",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0901_Watcher",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 9,
        "AchievementId": "S_culldrowned",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0901_0101_culldrowned_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0901_0101_culldrowned_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0901_0101_culldrowned_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0901_0101_culldrowned_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0901_0101_culldrowned_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0901_0101_culldrowned_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0901_0101_culldrowned_complete_availaible_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0901_0102_campandtools",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 1,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0901_0102_d_00_container_campandtools",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0901_Watcher",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 9,
        "AchievementId": "S_campandtools",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0901_0102_campandtools_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0901_0102_campandtools_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0901_0102_campandtools_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0901_0102_campandtools_proposal_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0901_0102_campandtools_proposal_next",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0901_0102_campandtools_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0901_0102_campandtools_complete_availaible_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0901_0103_boarproblem",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 2,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0901_0103_d_00_container_boarproblem",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0901_Watcher",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 9,
        "AchievementId": "S_boarproblem",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "S_campandtools",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0901_0103_boarproblem_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0901_0103_boarproblem_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0901_0103_boarproblem_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0901_0103_boarproblem_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0901_0103_boarproblem_incomplete",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0901_0103_boarproblem_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0901_0103_boarproblem_complete_availaible_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0901_0104_xmarksthespot",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0901_0104_d_00_container_xmarksthespot",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0901_Watcher",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 9,
        "AchievementId": "S_xmarksthespot_p1",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0901_0104_xmarksthespot_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0901_0104_xmarksthespot_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0901_0104_xmarksthespot_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0901_0104_xmarksthespot_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0901_0104_xmarksthespot_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0901_0104_xmarksthespot_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0901_0104_xmarksthespot_complete_availaible_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0901_0107_preciouscargo",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0901_0107_d_00_container_preciouscargo",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0901_Watcher",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 9,
        "AchievementId": "S_preciouscargo",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0901_0107_preciouscargo_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0901_0107_preciouscargo_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0901_0107_preciouscargo_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0901_0107_preciouscargo_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0901_0107_preciouscargo_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0901_0107_preciouscargo_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0901_0107_preciouscargo_complete_availaible_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0901_0108_introtosettlement",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 3,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0901_0108_d_00_container_introtosettlement",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0904_Overseer",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 9,
        "AchievementId": "S_introtosettlement",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0901_0108_introtosettlement_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0901_0108_introtosettlement_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0901_0108_introtosettlement_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0901_0108_introtosettlement_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0901_0108_introtosettlement_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0901_0108_introtosettlement_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0901_0108_introtosettlement_complete_availaible_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0925_0101_truffles",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 3,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0925_0101_d_00_container_truffles",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0425_HerbalistFL_Town",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 9,
        "AchievementId": "S_truffles",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0925_0101_truffles_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0425_0101_truffles_title",
        "Description": "@0425_0101_truffles_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0425_0101_truffles_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0425_0101_truffles_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0425_0101_truffles_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0425_0101_truffles_complete",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0904_01a01_warnmagistrate",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 3,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0904_01a01_d_00_container_warnmagistrate",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0902_Magistrate",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 9,
        "AchievementId": "S_warnmagistrate",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0904_01a01_warnmagistrate_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0904_01a01_warnmagistrate_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0904_01a01_warnmagistrate_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0904_0901_TheHermitFL_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0904_0901_TheHermitFL_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0904_01a01_warnmagistrate_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0904_01a01_warnmagistrate_complete_availaible_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0902_0101_hearthandhome",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 3,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0902_0101_d_00_container_hearthandhome",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0902_Magistrate",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 9,
        "AchievementId": "S_hearthhome",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0902_0101_hearthandhome_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0902_0101_hearthandhome_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0902_0101_hearthandhome_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0902_0101_hearthandhome_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0902_0101_hearthandhome_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0902_0101_hearthandhome_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0902_0101_hearthandhome_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0902_0102_intrototrader",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 4,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0902_0102_d_00_container_intrototrader",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0902_Magistrate",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 9,
        "AchievementId": "S_intrototrader",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0902_0102_intrototrader_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0902_0102_intrototrader_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0902_0102_intrototrader_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0902_0102_intrototrader_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0902_0102_intrototrader_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0902_0102_intrototrader_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0902_0102_intrototrader_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0902_0103_introtooverseer",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 4,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0902_0103_d_00_container_introtooverseer",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0904_Overseer",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 9,
        "AchievementId": "S_introtooverseer",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0902_0103_introtooverseer_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0902_0103_introtooverseer_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0902_0103_introtooverseer_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0902_0103_introtooverseer_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0902_0103_introtooverseer_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0902_0103_introtooverseer_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0902_0103_introtooverseer_complete_availaible_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0904_0104_overseersettlement",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 4,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0904_0104_d_00_container_overseersettlement",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0904_Overseer",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 9,
        "AchievementId": "S_overseersettlement",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0904_0104_overseersettlement_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0904_0104_overseersettlement_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0904_0104_overseersettlement_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0904_0104_overseersettlement_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0904_0104_overseersettlement_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0904_0104_overseersettlement_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0904_0104_overseersettlement_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0904_0103_introtoartificer",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 4,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0904_0103_d_00_container_introtoartificer",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0905_Artificer",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 9,
        "AchievementId": "S_introtoartificer",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0904_0103_introtoartificer_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0904_0103_introtoartificer_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0904_0103_introtoartificer_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0904_0103_introtoartificer_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0904_0103_introtoartificer_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0904_0103_introtoartificer_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0904_0103_introtoartificer_complete_availaible_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0905_0101_craftforartificer",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 5,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0905_0101_d_00_container_craftforartificer",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0905_Artificer",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 9,
        "AchievementId": "S_craftforartificer",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0905_0101_craftforartificer_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0905_0101_craftforartificer_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0905_0101_craftforartificer_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0905_0101_craftforartificer_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0905_0101_craftforartificer_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0905_0101_craftforartificer_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0905_0101_craftforartificer_complete_availaible_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0905_0102_campingunlock",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 5,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0905_0102_d_00_container_campingunlock",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0903_Survivalist",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 9,
        "AchievementId": "S_campingunlock",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0905_0102_campingunlock_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0905_0102_campingunlock_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0905_0102_campingunlock_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0905_0102_campingunlock_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0905_0102_campingunlock_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0905_0102_campingunlock_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0905_0102_campingunlock_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0903_0201_survivalistquest",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0903_0201_d_00_container_survivalistquest",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0903_Survivalist",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 9,
        "AchievementId": "S_magistratequest",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0903_0201_survivalistquest_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0903_0201_survivalistquest_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0903_0201_survivalistquest_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0903_0201_survivalistquest_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0903_0201_survivalistquest_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0903_0201_survivalistquest_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0903_0201_survivalistquest_complete_availaible_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0903_0202_returntomagistrate",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 6,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0903_0202_d_00_container_returntomagistrate",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0902_Magistrate",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 9,
        "AchievementId": "S_returntomagistrate",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0903_0202_returntomagistrate_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0903_0202_returntomagistrate_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0903_0202_returntomagistrate_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0903_0202_returntomagistrate_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0903_0202_returntomagistrate_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0903_0202_returntomagistrate_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0903_0202_returntomagistrate_complete_availaible_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0902_0202_introtoallfactions",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 6,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0902_0202_d_00_container_introtoallfactions",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 9,
        "AchievementId": "S_introtoallfactions",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "S_introtoallfactions_accepted",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0902_0202_introtoallfactions_success",
        "ObjectiveReward": "0909_0103_timetochoose",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0902_0202_introtoallfactions_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0902_0202_introtoallfactions_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0902_0202_introtoallfactions_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0902_0202_introtoallfactions_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0902_0202_introtoallfactions_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0902_0202_introtoallfactions_complete_availaible_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0907_0101_marauderquest1",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0907_0101_d_00_container_marauderquest1",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0907_Commander",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 9,
        "AchievementId": "S_marauderquest1",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "S_timetochoose",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0907_0101_marauderquest1_success",
        "ObjectiveReward": "9809_M_0001_RankUp",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": true,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0907_0101_marauderquest1_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0907_0101_marauderquest1_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0907_0101_marauderquest1_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0907_0101_marauderquest1_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0907_0101_marauderquest1_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0907_0101_marauderquest1_complete_availaible_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0908_0101_syndicatequest1",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0908_0101_d_00_container_syndicatequest1",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0908_Alchemist",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 9,
        "AchievementId": "S_syndicatequest1",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "S_timetochoose",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0908_0101_syndicatequest1_success",
        "ObjectiveReward": "9809_S_0001_RankUp",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": true,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0908_0101_syndicatequest1_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0908_0101_syndicatequest1_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0908_0101_syndicatequest1_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0908_0101_syndicatequest1_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0908_0101_syndicatequest1_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0908_0101_syndicatequest1_complete_availaible_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0909_0101_covenantquest1",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0909_0101_d_00_container_covenantquest1",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0909_Adjudicator",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 9,
        "AchievementId": "S_covenantquest1",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "S_timetochoose",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0909_0101_covenantquest1_success",
        "ObjectiveReward": "9809_C_0001_RankUp",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": true,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0909_0101_covenantquest1_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0909_0101_covenantquest1_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0909_0101_covenantquest1_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0909_0101_covenantquest1_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0909_0101_covenantquest1_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0909_0101_covenantquest1_complete_availaible_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0909_0103_timetochoose",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 6,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0909_0103_d_00_container_timetochoose",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 9,
        "AchievementId": "S_timetochoose",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "S_introtoallfactions",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0909_0103_timetochoose_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0909_0103_timetochoose_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0909_0103_timetochoose_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@prompt_DEFAULT",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0909_0103_timetochoose_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0909_0103_timetochoose_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0909_0103_timetochoose_complete_availaible_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0902_0401_factionhandoff",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 7,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0902_0401_d_00_container_factionhandoff",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0902_Magistrate",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 9,
        "AchievementId": "S_factionhandoff",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0902_0401_factionhandoff_success",
        "ObjectiveReward": "0904_0501_encroachingcorruption",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0902_0401_factionhandoff_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0902_0401_factionhandoff_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@prompt_DEFAULT",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0902_0401_factionhandoff_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0902_0401_factionhandoff_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0902_0401_factionhandoff_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0904_0501_encroachingcorruption",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 10,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0904_0501_d_00_container_encroachingcorruption",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0904_Overseer",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 9,
        "AchievementId": "S_encroachingcorruption",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "S_factionhandoff",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0904_0501_encroachingcorruption_success",
        "ObjectiveReward": "0904_0901_TheHermitFL",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0904_0501_encroachingcorruption_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0904_0501_encroachingcorruption_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0904_0501_encroachingcorruption_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0904_0501_encroachingcorruption_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0904_0501_encroachingcorruption_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0904_0501_encroachingcorruption_complete",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0910_0101_laidtorest",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0910_0101_d_00_container_laidtorest",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0910_Barkeep",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "09_Quest_01",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0910_0101_laidtorest_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@0910_0101_laidtorest_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0910_0101_laidtorest_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0910_0101_laidtorest_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0910_0101_laidtorest_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0910_0101_laidtorest_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0910_0101_laidtorest_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
        "QuestArcTag": "FirstLightArc1"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0903_0301_avoidopenflame",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0903_0301_d_00_container_avoidopenflame",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0903_Survivalist",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "09_Quest_04",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0903_0301_avoidopenflame_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@0903_0301_avoidopenflame_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0903_0301_avoidopenflame_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0903_0301_avoidopenflame_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0903_0301_avoidopenflame_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0903_0301_avoidopenflame_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0903_0301_avoidopenflame_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0910_0102_distillation",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0910_0102_d_00_container_distillation",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0910_Barkeep",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "09_Quest_02",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "09_Quest_01",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0910_0102_distillation_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@0910_0102_distillation_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0910_0102_distillation_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0910_0102_distillation_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0910_0102_distillation_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0910_0102_distillation_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0910_0102_distillation_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
        "QuestArcTag": "FirstLightArc1"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0904_0201_minerrequisition",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0904_0201_d_00_container_minerrequisition",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0904_Overseer",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "09_Quest_06",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "09_Quest_01",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0904_0201_minerrequisition_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@0904_0201_minerrequisition_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0904_0201_minerrequisition_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0904_0201_minerrequisition_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0904_0201_minerrequisition_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0904_0201_minerrequisition_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0904_0201_minerrequisition_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0905_0302_theoryoldworld",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0905_0302_d_00_container_theoryoldworld",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0905_Artificer",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "09_Quest_15",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "09_Quest_04",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0905_0302_theoryoldworld_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@0905_0302_theoryoldworld_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0905_0302_theoryoldworld_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0905_0302_theoryoldworld_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0905_0302_theoryoldworld_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0905_0302_theoryoldworld_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0905_0302_theoryoldworld_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0905_0301_evolutioncorruption_pt1",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0905_0301_d_00_container_evolutioncorruption_p1",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0905_Artificer",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "09_Quest_14",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "09_Quest_02",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0905_0301_evolutioncorruption_pt1_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@0905_0301_evolutioncorruption_pt1_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0905_0301_evolutioncorruption_pt1_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0905_0301_evolutioncorruption_pt1_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0905_0301_evolutioncorruption_pt1_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0905_0301_evolutioncorruption_pt1_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0905_0301_evolutioncorruption_pt1_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
        "QuestArcTag": "FirstLightArc1"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0902_0501_discardedmemories",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0902_0501_d_00_container_discardedmemories",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0902_Magistrate",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "09_Quest_10",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "09_Quest_15",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0902_0501_discardedmemories_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@0902_0501_discardedmemories_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0902_0501_discardedmemories_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0902_0501_discardedmemories_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0902_0501_discardedmemories_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0902_0501_discardedmemories_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0902_0501_discardedmemories_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0905_0305_evolutioncorruption_pt3",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0905_0305_d_00_container_evolutioncorruption_p3",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0905_Artificer",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "09_Quest_18",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0905_0305_evolutioncorruption_pt3_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@0905_0305_evolutioncorruption_pt3_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0905_0305_evolutioncorruption_pt3_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0905_0305_evolutioncorruption_pt3_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0905_0305_evolutioncorruption_pt3_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0905_0305_evolutioncorruption_pt3_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0905_0305_evolutioncorruption_pt3_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
        "QuestArcTag": "FirstLightArc1"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0902_0502_errorofways",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0902_0502_d_00_container_errorofways",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0902_Magistrate",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "09_Quest_11",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0902_0502_errorofways_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@0902_0502_errorofways_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0902_0502_errorofways_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0902_0502_errorofways_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0902_0502_errorofways_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0902_0502_errorofways_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0902_0502_errorofways_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
        "QuestArcTag": "FirstLightArc3"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0904_0301_muzzleorthrus",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0904_0301_d_00_container_muzzleorthrus",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0904_Overseer",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "09_Quest_07",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0904_0301_muzzleorthrus_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@0904_0301_muzzleorthrus_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0904_0301_muzzleorthrus_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0904_0301_muzzleorthrus_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0904_0301_muzzleorthrus_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0904_0301_muzzleorthrus_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0904_0301_muzzleorthrus_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
        "QuestArcTag": "FirstLightArc3"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0903_0401_skininthegame",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0903_0401_d_00_container_skininthegame",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0903_Survivalist",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "09_Quest_05",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "09_Quest_11",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0903_0401_skininthegame_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@0903_0401_skininthegame_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0903_0401_skininthegame_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0903_0401_skininthegame_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0903_0401_skininthegame_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0903_0401_skininthegame_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0903_0401_skininthegame_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0902_0503_abandonedresearch",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0902_0503_d_00_container_abandonedresearch",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0902_Magistrate",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "09_Quest_12",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "09_Quest_11",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0902_0503_abandonedresearch_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@0902_0503_abandonedresearch_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0902_0503_abandonedresearch_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0902_0503_abandonedresearch_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0902_0503_abandonedresearch_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0902_0503_abandonedresearch_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0902_0503_abandonedresearch_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0904_0302_snuffingcandle",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0904_0302_d_00_container_snuffingcandle",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0904_Overseer",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "09_Quest_08",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "09_Quest_12",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0904_0302_snuffingcandle_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@0904_0302_snuffingcandle_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0904_0302_snuffingcandle_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0904_0302_snuffingcandle_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0904_0302_snuffingcandle_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0904_0302_snuffingcandle_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0904_0302_snuffingcandle_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0905_0306_brightazothflame",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0905_0306_d_00_container_brightazothflame",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0903_Survivalist",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "09_Quest_19",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "09_Quest_12",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0905_0306_brightazothflame_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@0905_0306_brightazothflame_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0905_0306_brightazothflame_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0905_0306_brightazothflame_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0905_0306_brightazothflame_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0905_0306_brightazothflame_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0905_0306_brightazothflame_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0902_0601_dispatchtothefront",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0902_0601_d_00_container_dispatchtothefront",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0904_Overseer",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "09_Quest_13",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "09_Quest_08",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0902_0601_dispatchtothefront_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@0902_0601_dispatchtothefront_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0902_0601_dispatchtothefront_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0902_0601_dispatchtothefront_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0902_0601_dispatchtothefront_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0902_0601_dispatchtothefront_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0902_0601_dispatchtothefront_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
        "QuestArcTag": "FirstLightArc2"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0910_0201_zoneofcontrol",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0910_0201_d_00_container_zoneofcontrol",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0902_Magistrate",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "09_Quest_03",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "09_Quest_08",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0910_0201_zoneofcontrol_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@0910_0201_zoneofcontrol_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0910_0201_zoneofcontrol_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0910_0201_zoneofcontrol_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0910_0201_zoneofcontrol_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0910_0201_zoneofcontrol_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0910_0201_zoneofcontrol_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0904_0303_curseebonyhawk",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0904_0303_d_00_container_curseebonyhawk",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0904_Overseer",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "09_Quest_09",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "09_Quest_03",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0904_0303_curseebonyhawk_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@0904_0303_curseebonyhawk_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0904_0303_curseebonyhawk_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0904_0303_curseebonyhawk_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0904_0303_curseebonyhawk_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0904_0303_curseebonyhawk_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0904_0303_curseebonyhawk_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
        "QuestArcTag": "FirstLightArc2"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0905_0307_evolutioncorruption_pt4",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0905_0307_d_00_container_evolutioncorruption_p4",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0905_Artificer",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "09_Quest_20",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "09_Quest_13",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0905_0307_evolutioncorruption_pt4_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@0905_0307_evolutioncorruption_pt4_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0905_0307_evolutioncorruption_pt4_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0905_0307_evolutioncorruption_pt4_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0905_0307_evolutioncorruption_pt4_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0905_0307_evolutioncorruption_pt4_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0905_0307_evolutioncorruption_pt4_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
        "QuestArcTag": "FirstLightArc1"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0904_0801_reassuringmagistrate",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 25,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0904_0801_d_00_container_reassuringmagistrate",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0902_Magistrate",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "09_Quest_16",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "09_Quest_09",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0904_0801_reassuringmagistrate_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@0904_0801_reassuringmagistrate_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0904_0801_reassuringmagistrate_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0904_0801_reassuringmagistrate_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0904_0801_reassuringmagistrate_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0904_0801_reassuringmagistrate_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0904_0801_reassuringmagistrate_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0905_0701_artificersgratitude",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 25,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0905_0701_d_00_container_artificersgratitude",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0910_Barkeep",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "09_Quest_17",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "09_Quest_20",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0905_0701_artificersgratitude_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@0905_0701_artificersgratitude_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0905_0701_artificersgratitude_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0905_0701_artificersgratitude_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0905_0701_artificersgratitude_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0905_0701_artificersgratitude_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0905_0701_artificersgratitude_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
        "QuestArcTag": "FirstLightArc1"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0904_0901_TheHermitFL",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 12,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0904_0901_container_TheHermitFL",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9901_MSQ_Yonas",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "MSQ_00_Init",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9901_MSQ_TheHermit_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0904_0901_TheHermitFL_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0904_0901_TheHermitFL_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0904_0901_TheHermitFL_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0904_0901_TheHermitFL_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@NPC_DefaultDialogue_0904_01_Overseer",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9901_9901_TheHermit_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0922_1501_intrototravel",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 12,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0922_1501_d_00_container_intrototravel",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1222_Innkeep",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 9,
        "AchievementId": "S_intrototravel",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0922_1501_intrototravel_success",
        "ObjectiveReward": "0922_1502_returntravel",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@0922_1501_intrototravel_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0922_1501_intrototravel_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0922_1501_intrototravel_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0922_1501_intrototravel_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0922_1501_intrototravel_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0922_1501_intrototravel_complete_availaible_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0922_1502_returntravel",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 12,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0922_1502_d_00_container_returntravel",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0922_Innkeep",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 9,
        "AchievementId": "S_returntravel",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0922_1502_returntravel_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0922_1502_returntravel_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0922_1502_returntravel_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@prompt_DEFAULT",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0922_1502_returntravel_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0922_1502_returntravel_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0922_1502_returntravel_complete_availaible_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0901_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0901_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 9,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0902_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0902_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 9,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0903_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0903_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 9,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0904_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0904_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 9,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0905_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0905_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 9,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0906_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0906_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 9,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0907_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0907_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 9,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0901_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0901_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 9,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0902_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0902_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 9,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0903_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0903_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 9,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0904_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0904_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 9,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0905_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0905_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 9,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0906_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0906_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 9,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0907_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0907_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 9,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0901_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0901_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 9,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0902_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0902_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 9,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0903_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0903_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 9,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0904_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0904_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 9,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0905_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0905_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 9,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0906_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0906_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 9,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0907_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0907_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 9,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0930_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0930_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 9,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0931_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0931_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 9,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0932_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0932_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 9,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0933_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0933_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 9,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0934_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0934_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 9,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0935_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0935_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 9,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0936_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0936_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 9,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0960_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0960_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 9,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0961_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0961_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 9,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0962_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0962_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 9,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0963_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0963_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 9,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0964_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0964_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 9,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0965_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0965_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 9,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0966_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0966_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 9,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0960_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0960_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 9,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0961_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0961_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 9,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0962_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0962_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 9,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0963_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0963_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 9,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0964_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0964_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 9,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0965_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0965_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 9,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0966_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0966_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 9,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0960_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0960_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 9,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0961_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0961_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 9,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0962_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0962_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 9,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0963_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0963_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 9,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0964_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0964_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 9,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0965_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0965_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 9,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0966_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0966_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 9,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_09_H_01_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_09_H_01_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 9,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_09_H_02_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_09_H_02_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 9,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_09_H_03_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_09_H_03_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 9,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_09_PVP_Area1_Syndicate_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_09_PVP_Area1_Syndicate_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 9,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 1,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_09_PVP_Area2_Syndicate_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_09_PVP_Area2_Syndicate_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 9,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 1,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_09_PVP_Area3_Syndicate_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_09_PVP_Area3_Syndicate_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 9,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 1,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_09_PVP_Area1_Marauder_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_09_PVP_Area1_Marauder_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 9,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 1,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_09_PVP_Area2_Marauder_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_09_PVP_Area2_Marauder_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 9,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 1,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_09_PVP_Area3_Marauder_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_09_PVP_Area3_Marauder_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 9,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 1,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_09_PVP_Area1_Covenant_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_09_PVP_Area1_Covenant_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 9,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 1,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_09_PVP_Area2_Covenant_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_09_PVP_Area2_Covenant_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 9,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 1,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_09_PVP_Area3_Covenant_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_09_PVP_Area3_Covenant_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 9,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 1,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_09_PVP_PK_Marauder_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_09_PVP_PK_Marauder_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 9,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 1,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    }
]